In this clip we're going to learn how to improve our math skills, and don't fool yourself.
Just like I said in the other clip practice, practice, practice okay.
The first thing you could do is practice every day for 15-20 minutes especially if you don't have any homework.
You must practice a little bit every day.
I give my students homework and what I do is I give them twenty problems to do from one week to the next.
Maybe twenty five problems, but I expect them to do only 3 problems per day.
That's three times seven is twenty one or three times eight is twenty four, just three problems per day.
That way they get used to the idea that they must practice the mathematics every single day whether they have homework or not.
That's what makes the difference between the As and the Cs okay.
So also get together with one of your friends who knows their math really well and they could help you too.
Ask your teacher for help.
Ask for help.